RESUME



EDUCATION

MAR 2009 - DEC 2014

Degree in Computer Science

National University of San Juan - FCEFyN - ARG

Thesis still pending.
Current GPA: 8.6 of 10

MAR 2005 - DEC 2008

Electronic Technician

National University of San Juan - EIDFS - ARG GPA: 8.57 of 10.

SKILLS

Javascript

Angular 6/7

AngularJS

React

Java

Professional Skills: Git, Unit Testing, Scrum, Jira, Leadership, Collaboration, Problem Solving.

LENGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Professional working proficient

GONZALO TERZANO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Phone: (+549) 264 464 9709 | Email: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/gonzalo-terzano | Github: www.github.com/gonzadk

ABOUT ME

I'm a 29 years old Sr Frontend Developer from Argentina and currently based in Córdoba. I enjoy working on extensive teams and sharing my knowledge in order to help other people to achieve professional success. I am currently focused on improving my leadership skills and I am also an amateur basketball player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEB 2017 - Present

Software Development Engineer

McAfee - Córdoba, Argentina

Brief Description: Fullstack developer responsible for end-to-end app development. Leading three teams of 5-6 people each. Working also on an inner source library reducing considerable work time of multiple projects across the company.

FEB 2016 - JAN 2017

Web UI Developer

Globant - Córdoba, Argentina

Brief Description: Worked on a busy team, sometimes under pressure, making friendly & interactive projects of eLearning on short periods of time.

APR 2015 - JAN 2016

Fullstack Developer

TravelPAQ — San Juan, Argentina

Brief Description: Great startup Company in which I worked on backend and frontend technologies but where I also had to perform deployments and configuration tasks on the servers.

APR 2010 - JAN 2016

Teaching Assistant Professor

National University of San Juan, FCEFyN - San Juan, Argentina

Brief Description: Helped on practical classes and gave classes in some cases. It was the place where I discovered that I like teaching and helping people.

REFERENCES

SANCHEZ EDUARDO

Fullstack Developer and Scrum Master.

E: ceseduardo@gmail.com

OCHOA RODRIGO

Frontend Architect.

E: rodrigo.ariel.ochoa@gmail.com